keralites.net 2013-10-06

# Keralites Community Network - Related Useful Links

  | 

** Privacy Statement--Keralites.net  
**  
The privacy of our visitors to Keralites.net is important to us.

At Keralites.net, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit _Keralites.net, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. User information and or site activity data, including pages accessed, browsers, domains may be collected throughout the World Wide Web sites. This information is used for standard information purposes and to improve the site content and display. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons  
**We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site and Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the 

[ Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Log Files  
**As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

We also use third party advertisements on Keralites.net to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**DoubleClick DART cookies  
**We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements).  This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”).  The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey).  DART uses “non personally identifiable information”.  It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.  You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [ DoubleClick Dart Advertising Policy.](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx)  

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program.  Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

Keralites.net may disclose information in situations where we reasonably believe that it is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal proceedings against someone who is misusing the site, using the site without proper authorisation, is interfering with the rights of Keralites.net, or when Keralites.net believes that the law requires such disclosure. In addition, the information may be used to verify your compliance with the Keralites.net Web site Terms of Use.

By using or visiting this site, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by this Policy and the Keralites.net Terms of Use, both now and in the future.

|
